<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AINet Lab @ UEC</title>
    <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AINet Lab @ UEC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ainet-lab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>学術論文誌 - Journal Masashi Wakaiki, Katsuya Suto, and Izumi Masubuchi, “Cell Zooming with Masked Data for Off-Grid Small Cell Networks: Distributed Optimization Approach,” IEEE Transactions on Control Systems Technology, accepted. Katsuya Suto, Shinsuke Bannai, Koya Sato, Kei Inage, Koichi Adachi, and Takeo Fujii, “Image-Dri</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/member/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/member/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:  Screenshot    Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katsuya Suto</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/suto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/suto/</guid>
      <description>Katsuya Suto received the B.Sc. degree in computer engineering from Iwate University, Morioka, Japan, in 2011, and the M.Sc. and Ph.D. degrees in information science from Tohoku University, Sendai, Japan, in 2013 and 2016, respectively. He has worked as a Postdoctoral Fellow for Research Abroad, Japan Society for the Promotion of Science, in the Broadband Communications Research Lab., University of Waterloo, ON, Canada, from 2016 to 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>研究室配属情報</title>
      <link>https://ainet-lab.github.io/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainet-lab.github.io/application/</guid>
      <description>須藤研究室の紹介 本研究室に興味を持っていただきありがとうございます。 配属を希望する学生は応募フォームから面談の申し込みをお願いします。 他大学</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
